jaagore.com 2011-04-25

# Privacy Policy | Jaagore

We at Tata Global beverages Limited are committed to protecting your privacy as a visitor to our Website and take your privacy very seriously. By using this website, you consent to the terms of our privacy policy for the collection, use and disclosure of your personal information for the purpose set out below. We do not collect, use or disclose your personal information for any purpose other than those identified below, except with your prior consent or as required by the laws applicable in India. 

##### INFORMATION COLLECTION: 

When you register on our Website, you create your own personal profile. You may form relationships, send messages, perform searches and queries, form groups, share and transmit information and carry out a whole bunch of interactive activities. Your profile information as well as your name, email and photo (if submitted) are displayed on the website to enable you to connect with people on our Website. We may collect, store and use the following kind of personal data: 

  * Your profile information;
  * Information about your computer and about your visits to and the use of this website (including your IP address, geographical location, browser type, referral source. please insert any other personal information which would be accessed by Tata Global beverages through the website.
  * Information that would provide us with your purpose of registering with us;
  * Any other information that you may choose to send us.

##### USING YOUR PERSONAL DATA:

The personal data submitted by you on this website will be used for the following purposes:

  * To administer the website;
  * Improve your browsing experience by personalizing the website;
  * Enable your use of the services available on the website;
  * To send general commercial communications;
  * Where you submit personal information for publication on our website, we will publish such information or use the information in the manner you may permit us to use; and
  * Please include any other uses of the website users personal data.

##### SHARING YOUR INFORMATION WITH THIRD PARTIES: 

We allow you to share your personal information with third parties through our Website. We will not share your personal information without obtaining your prior consent. 

##### SECURITY FOR YOUR PERSONAL DATA 

We will take all the appropriate precautions and the requisite security measures to protect your personal information to prevent any unauthorized use, loss, misuse or alteration/ abuse of your personal information. We will store all the personal information you provide on our secure servers. However, as you may be possibly aware, data transmission over the internet is inherently insecure and we cannot guarantee the security of data sent over the internet. You are responsible for keeping your password and user details confidential. 

We restrict access of your personal information to our employees, contractors and agents who need to know this information in order to operate, develop or improve our services. These individuals are bound by the requisite confidentiality obligations in order to protect your personal information. 

##### THIRD PARTY LINKS 

This Website may contain links to third party websites that are not controlled by Tata Global beverages Limited. These third party links are available to you as a convenience and you agree to use these links at your own risk. Please be aware that Tata Global beverages Limited is not responsible for the content of third party websites linked to Tata Global beverages Limited. 

##### CHANGES TO THIS PRIVACY POLICY

Any changes to the Website’s Privacy Policy will be promptly communicated on this website. If you have any questions about our privacy policy or wish to update any of the personal information you have provided to us, please contact our representative at [XXXXX XXXX ]. 

##### CONTACTING THE WEBSITE 

If you have any questions about this privacy policy, you may contact us at [XXXXX XXXX ].
